afflictionclothingstore.com 2013-06-28

# Affliction Official Store

Onestop Internet, Inc. ("Onestop") operates this Web Site, pursuant to contractual agreements with Affliction ("Company"), the designer and manufacturer of products sold on this Web Site. Onestop and Company are not affiliates of one another and have no relationship with one another other than through these agreements. Both Onestop and Company ("we" or "us") recognize that you care how information about you is used and shared. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this Web Site. Please also review our Terms & Conditions which also govern your use of this Web Site. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms & Conditions.

YOU UNDERSTAND THAT BY USING THE WEB SITE YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND TO HAVE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED, USED, TRANSFERRED TO AND PROCESSED IN THE UNITED STATES.

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Web Site and, where applicable, through our Customer Service Department in connection with the operation of this Web Site, and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other Web sites that we operate or through other off-line means. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact our Customer Service Department as indicated below. 

* WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT ME IS COLLECTED AND STORED, AND HOW IS THAT INFORMATION USED? 

Personally Identifiable Information: We collect and store information that you enter into this Web Site or that you voluntarily provide to our Customer Service Department. For example, when you open an account or place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following personally identifiable information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date. This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations, and to provide customer service. This information also may be used for our own marketing and internal business purposes, and to contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have affirmatively opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this Web Site. You may also provide us information in User Content you post to the Web Site.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We collect and store certain other non-personally identifiable information automatically whenever you interact with this Web Site. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this Web Site. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Web Site and to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience.

In addition to ordering products and services through this Web Site, we may also offer you the opportunity to provide us with Testimonials. If you send a Testimonial to us through this Web Site, in addition to collecting and storing the information described above, we may print that Testimonial, or an excerpt from it, on this Web Site, or otherwise publish it, together only with your first name, the first letter of your last name, and partial location (city, state, and/or country).

* WHAT TECHNOLOGIES ARE USED TO COLLECT MY INFORMATION? 

Cookies: Like many Web sites, we use "cookies", which are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. Cookies help us to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this Web Site without checking out. Cookies are not used on this Web Site to store your account information; this information is stored securely on this Web Site's server. When you log in at this Web Site with your username and password, we will assign you a "secure session id." The server then passes your information to you through this secure session id. Also, we will use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of this Web Site. Cookies are also used to track the identity of the Web site you visited immediately prior to visiting this Web Site; otherwise, we do not track information about your use of other Web sites. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on this Web Site. We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources, to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you.

Log File Information: In addition to cookies, we may also collect and use "log file information" from you. Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you access or use the Web Site, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Web Site, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

Clear Gifs Information: When you use the Web Site, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make this Web Site better for our users.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our Web Site; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; and (h) track User Content and users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

* WITH WHOM DO YOU SHARE INFORMATION? 

We do not share with others, or sell or license to others, any personally identifiable information that you provide to us through this Web Site or through our Customer Service Department, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy.

We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, contacting customers who have not checked out to follow up on abandoned shopping carts or to see if there was a problem with their use of the site, Web Site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. We provide personally identifiable information to these third parties, but we authorize them to use this information only in connection with the services they perform.

We may release personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or if we determine that such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Onestop and/or Company, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or others.

We may share non-personally identifiable information with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personally identifiable information include the number of users who visited this Web Site during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this Web Site. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form.

As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might sell or buy other businesses or assets, including potentially other online retail operators. In such transactions, information about customers (including personally identifiable information) often is among the transferred assets. Under such circumstances, Onestop or Company, as the case may be, would to the extent practicable require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we may run contests, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on the Web Site together with a third party partner. If you provide information to such third parties, you give them permission to use it for the purpose of that Event and any other use that you approve. We cannot control third parties' use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events.

* IS INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM CHILDREN? 

This Web Site is not intended or directed to anyone under the age of 13. We do not sell or ship any items ordered through this Web Site directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 13, nor do we collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should use this Web Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us. Visitors between the ages of 13 and 18 must obtain permission from their parents or guardians before using this Web Site.

* WHAT STEPS ARE TAKEN TO KEEP PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION SECURE? 

We use various security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, to protect personal information that we collect. If you place an order through this Web Site, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an email address and password. You must provide an appropriate email address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personally identifiable information further, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel a password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of a password, please contact our Customer Service Department.

We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or guarantee that your information on the Web Site may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of our distributors, such as social networks. We are not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

* HOW CAN I ACCESS, CORRECT AND UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION? 

You can access, correct and update certain personal information that you have provided to us by clicking on "Update Account" within the "My Account" area of this Web Site. You may also e-mail us to review and revise the information we have on file for you at [legal@onestop.com](mailto:legal@onestop.com).

* CAN I INDICATE WHETHER OR NOT I WANT TO RECEIVE PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS? 

You will have an opportunity to change these selections by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional emails we send you. Additionally, you may contact our Customer Service Department or write to us at:

Onestop Internet, Inc. 3040 E Ana St., Rancho Dominguez, CA 90221.

Please note that any request to be removed from such mailing lists may take up to one (1) week to become effective. Even if you are removed from any such list, if you order online, we will send you an email confirming your order and may need to contact you by phone, email, or regular mail if we have questions about your order.

* WHAT HAPPENS WHEN I LINK TO OR FROM ANOTHER WEB SITE? 

This Web Site may contain links to Web sites operated by third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other Web sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Web Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that you visit.

If you have accessed this Web Site through a link from certain of our advertising or marketing partners, this Web Site may include a frame of the applicable advertising or marketing partner. Nevertheless, the information you provide to us through these framed Web pages is collected by us, and our use of this information is governed by this Privacy Policy.

* NOTIFICATION PROCEDURES 

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Web Site, as determined by us in our sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

* HOW WILL I BE INFORMED ABOUT CHANGES REGARDING THIS PRIVACY POLICY? 

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this Web Site notifying users of the changes. In some cases, we also may send an email notifying users of the changes. You should check this Web Site periodically to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred. When we change the policy in a material way, we will update the 'last modified' date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
